<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Personals on MinecraftForge Blog</title><link>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/</link><description>Recent content in Personals on MinecraftForge Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:15:02 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><author>matyrobbrt</author><title>OptiFine Alternatives</title><link>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/matyrobbrt/optifine-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:15:02 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/matyrobbrt/optifine-alternatives/</guid><summary>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about OptiFine and alternatives for it!</summary><description>OptiFine is known for breaking modded environments. In this post, we'll talk about some alternatives to it.</description></item><item><author>lex</author><title>Twitter</title><link>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/lex/twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 18:31:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/lex/twitter/</guid><summary>Some honest mistakes were made. Here&amp;rsquo;s what, how, why, and what we&amp;rsquo;re doing to prevent it from happening again.</summary><description>Some honest mistakes were made. Here's what, how, why, and what we're doing to prevent it from happening again.</description></item><item><author>curle</author><title>Promotion</title><link>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/curle/promotion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 18:31:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/curle/promotion/</guid><summary>Some internal changes have been ongoing for a while, so perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s time to unveil the new Project Manager of Forge.</summary><description>Some internal changes have been ongoing for a while, so perhaps it's time to unveil the new Project Manager of Forge.</description></item><item><author>sciwhiz12</author><title>What are Mappings: An Explainer</title><link>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/sciwhiz12/what-are-mappings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 12:20:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/sciwhiz12/what-are-mappings/</guid><summary>We take at look at one of Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s obstacles for modding: obfuscated names, and the innovation that is &lt;em>mappings&lt;/em>: a set of names laid on top of the obfuscated ones, which make modding Minecraft more bearable for developers of mods and tools alike.</summary><description>In this post, we take a look at the topic of mappings: a set of class, method, and field names. We discuss the nature of obfuscated names and the problems they cause, and introduce the concepts of intermediate mappings and human-readable mappings and how they fix the problems of obfuscated mappings. We also briefly discuss how mappings are present in the development and production environments of Minecraft, and interspersed throughout the post are examples of the various mappings in play throughout the Minecraft modding community, including Mojmaps.</description></item><item><author>Forge Team</author><title/><link>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/cpw/aboutsigning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.minecraftforge.net/personal/cpw/aboutsigning/</guid><summary>title: &amp;ldquo;About signing&amp;rdquo; date: 2023-06-29T13:10:31-04:00 draft: true categories: author: cpw summary: &amp;ldquo;signing jars&amp;rdquo; description: &amp;ldquo;about signing jars&amp;rdquo; About JAR signing I&amp;rsquo;m writing this post to try and clear up some misconceptions about jar signing. What can it do, what can&amp;rsquo;t it do, why do we recommend it. Finally, I&amp;rsquo;ll try and put together some resources for getting started.
What is JAR signing? Jar signing is the act of generating a cryptographic signature for each member of a jar file.</summary><description/></item></channel></rss>